adhysteria.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy

The only destination for Free Hi Definition Video Classifieds , Photo classifieds and Video Auctions <meta name="abstract" content="Free" social="" video="" classifieds="" ,="" photo="" with="" auctions="">  
|   
---  
  
| 

|  _Adhysteria.com Privacy Policy_  
---  
  
This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the Adhysteria.com website (“Adhysteria.com”) work and to keep it safe (details below). In formal terms, Adhysteria.com.com, Unit 310, Balarama, and Bandra Mumbai India acting itself and through its subsidiaries, is the “data controller” of your personal information. This policy is effective June 1st 2007. Information posted on Adhysteria.com is obviously publicly available  
We collect and store the following personal information: 

* email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information;  
* Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Adhysteria.com and ad data (all through cookies – you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site);  
* other information, including users IP address   
_**Use**_  
  
We use users’ personal information to:   
* provide our services;  
* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;  
* encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;  
* customize users’ experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;  
* communicate marketing and promotional offers to you;  
* do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

|   
_**Disclosure**_  
  
We don’t sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without user’s explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with:   
* corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).  
* service providers who help with our business operations. 

|   
_**Using Information from Adhysteria.com**_  
  
You may use personal information gathered from Adhysteria.com only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn’t agreed to that   
  
_**Access, Modification, and Deletion**_  
  
You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page.   
Contact customer support by posting in the form to review any personal information we store that is not available on Adhysteria.com. There may a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back.   
  
_**Security**_  
  
We use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but as you probably know, nothing’s perfect, so we make no guarantees.   
  
_**General**_  
  
We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to in the contact us form   
  
_**Users**_  
  
By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Adhysteria.com we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.   
  
**_Listing Policy_**  
  
**For use of our Services, our rules are that you shall not post classifieds aimed at selling items or services that are illegal.**  
**Prohibited Items Policy.**  
**We specifically prohibit posting classifieds in relation to the following items:**

  * Alcoholic Beverages
  * Blood, Bodily Fluids and Body Parts 
  * Burglary Tools 
  * Counterfeit Items 
  * Illegal Drugs & Drug Paraphernalia 
  * Hazardous, Restricted, and Perishable Items 
  * Fireworks, Destructive Devices and Explosives 
  * Identity Documents, Personal Financial Records & Personal Information (in any form, including mailing lists) 
  * Lottery Tickets, Sweepstakes Entries and Slot Machines 
  * Obscene Material and Child Pornography 
  * Offensive Material 
  * Pesticides 
  * Police Badges and Uniforms 
  * Prescription Drugs and Devices 
  * Stocks and Other Securities 
  * Stolen Property 
  * Tobacco Products 
  * Weapons and related items (such as firearms, firearm parts and magazines, ammunition, BB and pellet guns, tear gas, stun guns, switchblade knives, and martial arts weapons) 
  * "Pyramid schemes" and "Multilevel Marketing“ 

**_Adult Policy_**  
  
Under Indian law it may be a criminal offense for you to buy or sell certain types of films, publications and computer games.   
As a guide, the following types of mature audience items may be illegal to buy or sell through posting of classifieds on the Site: 

  * Films which do not have a certificate for public exhibition issued by the Central Board of Film Certification 
  * Internationally released versions of Films, publications, or computer games that significantly differ from the domestic release; 
  * Items that describe, depict, express or otherwise deal with matters of sex, drug misuse or addiction, cruelty, violence or revolting or abhorrent phenomena in such a way that they offend against the standards of morality, decency and propriety generally accepted by reasonable adults; 
  * Items which contain an indecent representation of women within the meaning of the Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, 1986; 
  * Any publication or film or item that describes or depicts a minor who is, or who appears to be, under 18 (whether the minor is engaged in sexual activity or not). This material is generally described as child pornography; 
  * In the case of computer games, that are unsuitable for a minor to see or play. 

Apart from an item's classification, when considering whether a publication/item should be allowed on our Site, we consider the overall content of the listing, including pictures and text. For example, if an item description leads us to believe the content of the listing is not permitted as defined by this Policy, that item will be ended. Please note that blocking the questionable parts of an image will not exempt the item from these standards. Users who list classifieds relating to inappropriate items in this category may be suspended and are liable to be prosecuted.   
  
**Mature Audience/Sexually oriented material**  
  
Classifieds relating to items that are intended for use in a sexual setting (including "bondage" and "fetish" items,) display sexual activity or portray human genitalia in a "life-like" or realistic fashion are not allowed and will be ended by Rajiv. An example of such classifieds relating to an item not normally permitted would be a classified for the sale of a vibrator intended for use in sexual activity (massagers are OK). Please also be aware that titles with graphic adult language are inappropriate, regardless of the item contained in the listing itself.   
i. Without prejudice to the generality of the above, Rajiv does not permit posting or listing of classifieds in relation to the following: 

  * "Securities" within the meaning of the Securities Contract Regulation Act, 1956, including shares, bonds, debentures, etc. and/or any other financial instruments/assets of any description. 
  * Living, dead creatures and/or the whole or any part of any animal which has been kept or preserved by any means whether artificial or natural including rugs, skins, specimens of animals, antlers, horns, hair, feathers, nails, teeth, musk, eggs, nests, other animal products of any description the sale and purchase of which is prevented or restricted in any manner by applicable laws (including those prohibited under The Wildlife Protection Act, 1972). 
  * Weapons of any description. 
  * Liquor, tobacco products, drugs, psychotropic substances, narcotics, intoxicants of any description, medicines, palliative/curative substances. 
  * Religious items, including books, artifacts, etc. of any description or any other such item which is likely to affect the religious sentiments of any person. 
  * "Antiquities" and "Art Treasures" in violation of the provisions of the Antiquities and Art Treasures Act, 1972 ("the Act"). 
  * Used cellular phone SIM Cards or telecom services of any nature. . 

ii. shall not be defamatory, trade libelous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing;   
iii. shall not be obscene or contain pornography or contain an "indecent representation of women" within the meaning of the Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, 1986;   
iv. shall not contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancel bots, easter eggs or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information;   
v. shall not create liability for us or cause us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISPs or other suppliers; and   
vi. shall not link directly or indirectly to or include descriptions of items, goods or services that are prohibited under any applicable law for the time being in force including but not limited to the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1940, the Drugs And Magic Remedies (Objectionable Advertisements) Act, 1954, the Indian Penal Code, 1860.   
Also, you are not allowed to libel anyone or include “hate speech” directed at individuals or groups in your postings. You should not harass abuse, threaten, or advocate violence against other users or individuals or groups.   
Rajiv offers this platform as a vehicle for communicating about non-work oriented topics of common interest – buying and selling things, community events, etc. Please don’t use it to discuss work-related topics, which should be handled through traditional channels. Note that postings are solely the responsibility of the individual poster, and Rajiv does not endorse any posting or point of view expressed on this Site. We may elect to flag [and remove] postings that they find offensive, miscategorized, spam, or no longer current.
